<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on bendb</title><link>https://www.bendb.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on bendb</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2020. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:08:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bendb.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SSH Setup for Multiple Github Accounts</title><link>https://www.bendb.com/blog/ssh-with-multiple-github-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:08:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bendb.com/blog/ssh-with-multiple-github-accounts/</guid><description>Scenario: You&amp;rsquo;re starting at a new company, and they use GitHub for source control. This is nice, because you know GitHub. This is not nice, on the other hand, because you already use it for personal projects. Bad things can happen when you mix the personal and the professional, and you&amp;rsquo;d like to avoid even the appearance of impropriety. Time for a second GitHub account!
This is great, until you want to keep working on your personal things at the same time.</description></item><item><title>OkHttp 3.X on Android 4.4.4</title><link>https://www.bendb.com/blog/okhttp-3.x-on-android-4.4.4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 14:54:29 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bendb.com/blog/okhttp-3.x-on-android-4.4.4/</guid><description>This morning I was greeted at work by an unexpectedly-large number of crashes from a new Android release. As it happens, OkHttp 3.X has issues on Android 4.4.4 and 4.4.2 - it cannot reliably load the system&amp;rsquo;s default TrustManagers without looping and eventually crashing with an OutOfMemoryError. The fix was simple - we can reliably load it ourselves, and provide it to new OkHttpClient instances. For posterity, the solution we hit on follows below:</description></item><item><title>happy code</title><link>https://www.bendb.com/blog/happy-code/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 21:42:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.bendb.com/blog/happy-code/</guid><description>My favorite parts of being a programmer are those moments when, after ruminating on a bit of not-quite-clean code, elegant solutions just present themselves to you. Today&amp;rsquo;s installment is from Thrifty, the Thrift implementation for Android I wrote at Microsoft.
Briefly, part of Thrifty&amp;rsquo;s job is to generate Java classes corresponding to structs defined in Thrift IDL. Part of that is generating descriptive .toString() methods. For the first release, Thrifty generated code like this:</description></item><item><title>Hello Again, World!</title><link>https://www.bendb.com/blog/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:15:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bendb.com/blog/hello-world/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the dawn of a new era! After trying and failing to keep a Ghost blog up and running, I&amp;rsquo;ve had enough. I&amp;rsquo;m throwing in the towel, admitting defeat, and joining the legions of static-site-generators out there. Welcome to my new Hugo blog. Expect the same level of content as before, with much less downtime!
While I&amp;rsquo;ll miss the experience of writing in Ghost&amp;rsquo;s lovely editor, here&amp;rsquo;s a list of things I won&amp;rsquo;t miss:</description></item></channel></rss>